<PresidentText>
	<President name="Carl">
		*No information given or found*
	</President>
	<President name="Blingfaster">
		Mrs. Blatcher fired one of the assistants only to
		cram his office full of tea, sugar and biscuits.
	</President>
	<President name="Bob">
		Mr. Cake's office wall is decorated with no less 
		than forty-two rifles. Standing in there... it's 
		amazing and nerve-racking at the same time.
	</President>
	<President name="Burt">
		Mr. Kumar-Rajif has lived a hard life. He lost two 
		toes in the jungle trying to escape a crazed eel. 
		Oh, and also he's mute.
	</President>
	<President name="Dhelma">
		Don't let her kind appearance fool you... 
		This lady's heart is made of iron. Once, she called 
		her assistant "fool".
	</President>
	<President name="Flaire">
		With an unsuccessful career in the film industry, 
		Ms. Garbo instead turned her attention towards presidency. 
		There were speculations about electoral fraud when the 
		body guards shared high-fives after the inaugural address.
	</President>
	<President name="Frank">
		Rumours say Mr. Funk's hair isn't natural. 
		I think it is, but some kind of structure in 
		there is holding it all up.
	</President>
	<President name="Frankie">
		We don't know how she does it, but Ms. Won Gi can
		perform all her presidential duties while playing
		computer games. Our scientists are looking into it.
	</President>
	<President name="Gramma">
		Mrs. Raisin is closer to her death than her 90's.
		That's all we know.
	</President>
	<President name="Hans">
		Mrs. Raynd has a quite queer look on the working class. 
		She thinks every single one of them is a bum.
	</President>
	<President name="Heinrich">
		Mr. Smith used to work as a math teacher. How he
		got from there to presidency is a mystery.
	</President>
	<President name="Hugo">
		Komandant von Schnitzel's jacket is always clean. 
		How this is possible is a mystery, but some have 
		speculated that he keeps spares hidden in his desk.
	</President>
	<President name="Ludo">
		Larry never tells anyone why he's sad. It's really annoying, 
		since he breaks down every seven seconds and we can't comfort
		him because we don't know what's wrong.
	</President>
	<President name="Nojiko">
		Mr. Ringu-san's eyes are terrible to behold. Most of us here 
		in office don't focus on that, though, since Mr. Ringu-san has 
		a way of staring with his teeth instead.
	</President>
	<President name="no-nose">
		Yes, Mr. Scarecrow has indeed tried working as a scarecrow. 
		No, he was not very effective.
	</President>
	<President name="Sam">
		Mr. Hamilton smells nice. Every day. Even when he's supposed 
		to smell bad he smells nice. How does it even work?
	</President>
	<President name="Sarah">
		We here in office has made a habit of leaving a polished apple 
		on Ms. Plum's desk every morning. There's no good explanation, 
		but it feels like we're supposed to, somehow.
	</President>
	<President name="Stieg">
		Due to a tragic accident when he was in the army, Mr. Poirot 
		can't remove his mask. Don't worry though; we have a team of 
		interpreters working around the	clock with him.
	</President>
	<President name="Sture" frames="4" timeout="10000" directory="Sture/">
		When Mr. Mash says jump, you don't ask why. You ask how high.
	</President>
	<President name="Will">
		Built from a bunch of old toasters and microwaves,
		this tin man really hates communists.
	</President>
	<President name="Alva">
		G.S. Borgia doesn't take kindly to the nickname "tin can". 
		Please refrain from using it. In fact, a list of nicknames 
		G.S. Borgia doesn't care for can be acquired from her technician.
	</President>
	<President name="Boris">
		Don't stand too close to G.S. Boris or he'll bite you in the face. 
		He probably got this behaviour from his father, who was a bear.
	</President>
	<President name="Gustav">
		G.S. Zelezo's moustache is a thing of legends. 
		Many have tried to copy it; none have succeeded.
	</President>
	<President name="Olga">
		Some say G.S. Zheng is a descendant of a great pirate lord, 
		but it has never been confirmed. What we do know for sure 
		is that she's scary.
	</President>
	<President name="SiB">
		G.S. "SiB" doesn't have a particularly wide vocabulary. 
		Fhtagn here, fhtagn there – we usually just assume he's 
		pleased with our work.
	</President>
</PresidentText>